## **David Campbell**

davidcampbell2313@gmail.com 206-549-9290

## Profile

Information systems leader and manager with considerable experience in colleges, universities, and state agencies. Experience ranges from systems engineering and support to management of teams of professionals. Broad exposure to technologies provides versatility and adaptability to a variety of environments. Commitment to diversity is backed up by personal experiences.

## Experience

University of Washington, December 2009 - March 2021

- Developed custom web application for tracking student and faculty data for multiple schools using ASP.NET and SQL Server
- Technical lead in transition from proprietary database to GIS map database for grant-based project
- Created Arboretum map web applications using ArcGIS Server, Dojo, and javascript
- Developed educational registration system for outreach programs at UW Botanic Gardens using ASP.NET, C# and SQL Server
- Developed volunteer and activity tracking web applications for UW Botanic Gardens using PHP and MySQL
- Developed custom PHP/MySQL web applications for research-based organizations
- Technical lead in transition from HTML/CSS website to WordPress school website
- Advised graduate students in healthcare informatics program

Seattle Central College, August 2003 - November 2008

- Managed over 100 server-based desktop applications for over 500 educational lab workstations
- Managed instructional equipment including digitizing tables, large format printers, MIDI equipment, and physics measuring tools
- Developed stabile desktop operating system images for more than 1500 faculty, staff, and student workstations
- Provided workshops for students on specific software topics
- Managed assistive technology for disabled students and ESL software for international students

Academix Consultation Services, January 1995 - March 2003

- Led projects at the Washington State Housing Finance Commission and the Department of Transportation
- Designed and implemented server and workstation projects for various healthcare and legal clients
- Supervised teams of technicians providing technical support and project implementation
- Provided full documentation of networks and software, including vulnerabilities
- Taught courses in productivity software including Microsoft Office applications

## Skills and Technologies

PHP/MySQL, ASP.NET, C#, SQL Server, HTML/CSS, javascript, Python, Java, Powershell, ArcGIS, MIDI

Azure, Windows Active Directory, Linux/Unix, Microsoft Office Applications, Visual Basic

Education

Antioch Graduate School, Graduate Studies University of Washington, Bachelor of Arts